question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together"
                 " to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr."
                 " and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot;"
                 " before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo"
                 " buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }
]
